http://www.linak-us.com/privacy-policy/

Home
Privacy policy
LINAK Privacy Policy
Please read our Privacy Policy carefully. By continuing to use our services, it is assumed that you accept the terms and conditions of our privacy policy.
Thank you for spending time reading our Privacy Policy. With this policy we will explain what, how, and why we collect information when you communicate with us, use our services, or visit our website. We also describe the specific ways we use and disclose the information. We fully respect all wishes for confidentiality of personal data that is disclosed to us and we are aware of the need for appropriate protection and management of any personal data we receive. We will never sell information about you and other users.
Who are we?The LINAK Group is an international company engaged in designing and manufacturing electric linear actuator systems. LINAK A/S is based in Guderup, Denmark and is represented in several countries all over the world through either subsidiaries or distributors. See a list of the LINAK group of companies here: LINAK subsidiaries and distributors worldwide .
The website is controlled by LINAK A/S, unless it identifies in its terms or otherwise that it is controlled by another LINAK entity.
What personal data do we collect about you?LINAK collects personally identifiable information such as names, addresses, email addresses, phone numbers (if provided), and the interest you have in our products. These types of data are only collected when you provide such data voluntarily to us and/or when you have given your consent.
We may collect other types of data in various ways: LINAK records information submitted via the contact form on the webpages for the purpose of processing your comments, questions, or suggestions or when you subscribe to our newsletters.
We automatically collect data about your visits to and usage of our website. The personal data may include your IP address, operating system and platform, type of browser, browsing activity and other data on how you interacted with our website, such as clicks you have made on LINAK ads prior to visiting our webpages and/or contact forms.
We work together with third parties (including business partners, sub-contractors, analytics providers and search information providers) and may receive anonymous information from them. Our distributor of online newsletters tracks your activities when opening the newsletter.
We kindly ask you not to send us any sensitive personal data, such as information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometric or genetic characteristics, criminal background, or trade union membership. We will not collect such data from you unless you give us your consent or we are required by law.
Our business and related services and related webpages are not intended for or designed to attract children.
How we may use your personal data:Your data may be processed for the following purposes:
To contact you regarding sales and services
To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with products and services that you request from us
To contact you regarding events and invitations to trade fairs;
To carry out surveys about how to improve our service to you
To improve our services
To customize and optimize our marketing activities so that you only get information within your field of interest; or
for other purposes directly requested by you.
Who we share your personal data with:LINAK may disclose your personal information internally to any LINAK group company for the use and purposes listed above. The reason is that we aim to give you the best service. Your personal data is only shared with employees who have a work-related need to access your data in order to carry out their tasks.
We may also disclose your personal information to third parties, when we:
Use third-party entities for the hosting of our website and other services
Use an external email marketing system to handle newsletters on different marketing and sales topics
Use third parties in events for which you register to facilitate your participation in such events
Manage your personal data in LINAK Group’s CRM system;
Process orders in LINAK Group’s ERP system using a minimum of your personal data;
Make arrangements with external logistics providers and other service providers
Use an external customer experience system to collect feedback on how LINAK performs; or
when we are obligated to disclose your personal data under applicable laws and regulations, which may include laws outside your country of residence
LINAK uses third-party data processors. Third-party data processors cooperate with us in the provision of the content and services you request. In doing so they safeguard the confidentiality of your data and apply the necessary technical and organizational measures. We regularly adapt our safety precautions to ongoing technical developments.
Your personal data will also be processed by our external partners outside the EU. We apply the required legal safeguards in these data exchanges with service partners from non-EU countries.
How we use Cookies and Third-Party Connections on our webpage:We process data collected by cookies in order to:
Operate, improve, and optimize the performance and user experience of the website and its services
Collect anonymous feedback and usage data to improve our understanding of users, and to provide better and tailored website services;
Enhance security and to block possible spam;
Build statistics;
Provide personalized advertising: We and our advertising partners use social media tracking tools such as Facebook Pixel and LinkedIn Pixel; or
when we collect data when you use our webpage to find out how our online offering is used. We use this information and other personal information to improve our services and for personalized advertising on various platforms.
For more information about cookies, please read our Cookie Policy which you will find on our website. You can at any time change or withdraw your consent from cookies and third-party connections via the cookie policy on our website.
We can in some countries send you marketing material on products similar to those you have previously ordered, however, you can at any time opt out of such communication by unsubscribing.
If you have subscribed to our newsletter, we will use ClickDimensions to send email newsletters, which include web tracking. Tracking gives us insight into whether you access our website through links in the newsletter and how you use our website. We can see which pages you have clicked on and how long time you spent on a certain page. This helps us better understand your needs as a user of our website and enables us to maintain and build our website in accordance with user’s needs. Through tracking we may also identify possible interest in specific products, and we may contact you to follow up on your interest. You can opt out of ClickDimensions web tracking via marketing cookies in our cookie policy. For further details, please see the ClickDimensions Privacy Policy.
How we use social media platforms: In order to optimize our activities on social media platforms, such as LinkedIn and Facebook, we use tools such as lead ads and Facebook Custom Audiences, which means that we pay for the platform to assist us in finding relevant persons to target our content to, based on registered interests or earlier visited pages collected by the platform. Criteria used for targeting our content are either set by us or the social media platform. Such sponsored ads are marked “Sponsored” in the social media platform. If you interact with our posts, we will note this communication.
How long we store your data for: LINAK will keep your personal data only for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purpose for which it was collected. LINAK may have to store data in order to comply with a legal retention requirement. We may keep data in an anonymized form for statistical purposes rather than deleting your data.
How we protect your data: We have taken appropriate technical and operational security precautions to protect your data from being accidentally or intentionally manipulated, lost, destroyed, or accessed by unauthorized persons. Our security measures are reviewed regularly. We will update these measures in order to keep up with technological advances.
Your data rights: You may opt out of receiving marketing-related emails from us at any given time by using the unsubscribe link in the marketing material. We will comply with your request immediately thereafter. You have to actively delete the cookies set on your PC. If you leave the cookie set by our webpage supplier, Sitecore, LINAK will continue to receive statistical data about your visits to our webpage, and this will be linked to your name and email address in our system. These statistical data will be deleted upon your request.
If you have comments or questions related to how we process your personal data or if you want to access, update, amend, or erase any of your personal data, you can contact us here.
Our postal address is: LINAK A/S Smedevænget 8, Guderup DK-6430 Nordborg, Denmark Denmark Company Registration Number: 66365328
If you are of the opinion that we process or have processed your personal data illegally, you may lodge a complaint with the Danish Data Protection Supervisory Authority (Datatilsynet), Borgergade 28, 5., DK-1300 Copenhagen K or the supervisory authority of your country of nationality.
Changes:We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. All updates and amendments will be uploaded to the websites.
You must accept the Terms of use to download.
